http://www.practicetechnologies.com/privacy.html

Privacy
Your privacy is very important to us. Accordingly, we have developed this Policy in order for you to understand how we collect, use, communicate and make use
of personal information. The following outlines our Privacy Policy.
When accessing our Website, RPCD Holdings, LLC will learn certain information about you during your visit.
Similar to other commercial Web sites, our Web site utilizes a standard technology
called "cookies" (see explanation below, "What Are Cookies?") and Web server logs to collect information about how our Web site is used. Information gathered through cookies and Web server logs may include the date and time of visits, the pages viewed, time spent at our Web site, and the Web sites visited just before and just after our Web site, your IP address.
What Are Cookies?
A cookie is a very small text document, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier. When you visit a Web site, that site's computer asks your computer for permission to store this file in a part of your hard drive specifically designated for cookies. Each Web site can send its own cookie to your browser if your browser's preferences allow it, but (to protect your privacy) your browser only permits a Web site to access the cookies it has already sent to you, not the cookies sent to you by other sites.
IP Addresses
IP addresses are used by your computer every time you are connected to the Internet. Your IP address is a number that is used by computers on the network to identify your computer. IP addresses are automatically collected by our web server as part of demographic and profile data known as “traffic data” so that data (such as the Web pages you request) can be sent to you.
Email Information
If you choose to correspond with us through email, we may retain the content of your email messages together with your email address and our responses. We provide the same protections for these electronic communications that we employ in the maintenance of information received online, mail and telephone.
How Do We Use the Information That You Provide to Us?
Broadly speaking, we use personal information for purposes of administering our business activities, providing customer service and making available other items and services to our customers and prospective customers.
RPCD Holdings, LLC will not obtain personally-identifying information about you when you visit our site, unless you choose to provide such information to us, nor will
such information be sold or otherwise transferred to unaffiliated third parties without the approval of the user at the time of collection.
We may disclose information when legally compelled to do so, in other words, when we, in good faith, believe that the law requires it or for the protection of our legal rights.
A Special Note About Children
Children are not eligible to use our web site and services and we ask that minors (under the age of 13) do not submit any personal information to us. If you are a minor, you can use this site only in conjunction with permission and guidance from your parents or guardians.
How Do We Protect Your Information and Secure Information Transmissions?
Email is not recognized as a secure medium of communication. For this reason, we request that you do not send private information to us by email. However, doing so is allowed, but at your own risk. Some of the information you may enter on our Web site may be transmitted securely via a secure medium known as Secure Sockets Layer, or SSL. Credit Card information is never transmitted via email.
RPCD Holdings, LLC may use software programs to create summary statistics, which are used for such purposes as assessing the number of visitors to the different sections of our site, what information is of most and least interest, determining technical design specifications, and identifying system performance or problem areas.
For site security purposes and to ensure that this service remains available to all users, RPCD Holdings, LLC uses software programs to monitor network traffic to identify unauthorized attempts to upload or change information, or otherwise cause damage.
Policy Changes
We reserve the right to amend this privacy policy at any time with or without notice. However, please be assured that if the Privacy Policy changes in the future, we will not use the personal information you have submitted to us under this Privacy Policy in a manner that is materially inconsistent with this Privacy Policy, without your prior consent.
We are committed to conducting our business in accordance with these principles in order to ensure that the confidentiality of personal information is protected and maintained.
Contact
Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please call us at (818) 502-5015 or send us an email at support@practicetechnologies.com
Terms Of Use
By accessing this web site, you are agreeing to be bound by these web site
Terms and Conditions of Use, all applicable laws and regulations, and agree
that you are responsible for compliance with any applicable local laws. If you
do not agree with any of these terms, you are prohibited from using or accessing
this site. The materials contained in this web site are protected by applicable
copyright and trade mark law.
Intellectual Property Rights
All copyrights, trademarks, patents and other intellectual property rights
in and on our website and all content and software located on the site shall
remain the sole property of RPCD Holdings, LLC or its licensors. The use of our trademarks,
content and intellectual property is forbidden without the express written consent
from RPCD Holdings, LLC.
You must not:
* Republish material from our website without prior written consent.
* Sell or rent material from our website.
* Reproduce, duplicate, create derivative, copy or otherwise exploit material on our website for any purpose.
* Redistribute any content from our website, including onto another website.
Acceptable Use
You agree to use our website only for lawful purposes, and in a way that does
not infringe the rights of, restrict or inhibit anyone else's use and enjoyment
of the website. Prohibited behavior includes harassing or causing distress or
inconvenience to any other user, transmitting obscene or offensive content or
disrupting the normal flow of dialogue within our website.
You must not use our website to send unsolicited commercial communications.
You must not use the content on our website for any marketing related purpose
without our express written consent.
Restricted Access
We may in the future need to restrict access to parts (or all) of our website
and reserve full rights to do so. If, at any point, we provide you with a username
and password for you to access restricted areas of our website, you must ensure
that both your username and password are kept confidential.
Revisions
RPCD Holdings, LLC may change these terms from time to time and so you should check these
terms regularly. Your continued use of our website will be deemed acceptance
of the updated or amended terms. If you do not agree to the changes, you should
cease using our website immediately.
If any of these terms are determined to be illegal, invalid or otherwise unenforceable,
it shall be severed and deleted from these terms and the remaining terms shall
survive and continue to be binding and enforceable.
Limitation of Liability
THE MATERIALS AT THIS SITE ARE PROVIDED "AS IS" WITHOUT ANY EXPRESS
OR IMPLIED WARRANTY OF ANY KIND INCLUDING WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, NONINFRINGEMENT
OF INTELLECTUAL PROPERTY, OR FITNESS FOR ANY PARTICULAR PURPOSE. IN NO EVENT
SHALL RPCD Holdings, LLC OR ITS AGENTS OR OFFICERS BE LIABLE FOR ANY DAMAGES WHATSOEVER
(INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, DAMAGES FOR LOSS OF PROFITS, BUSINESS INTERRUPTION,
LOSS OF INFORMATION, INJURY OR DEATH) ARISING OUT OF THE USE OF OR INABILITY
TO USE THE MATERIALS, EVEN IF RPCD Holdings, LLC HAS BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF
SUCH LOSS OR DAMAGES.
Disclaimer
RPCD Holdings, LLC makes no representations, warranties, or assurances as to the accuracy, currency or completeness of the content contain on this website or any sites linked to this site.
Limitation of Liability
THE MATERIALS AT THIS SITE ARE PROVIDED "AS IS" WITHOUT ANY EXPRESS
OR IMPLIED WARRANTY OF ANY KIND INCLUDING WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, NONINFRINGEMENT
OF INTELLECTUAL PROPERTY, OR FITNESS FOR ANY PARTICULAR PURPOSE. IN NO EVENT
SHALL RPCD Holdings, LLC OR ITS AGENTS OR OFFICERS BE LIABLE FOR ANY DAMAGES WHATSOEVER
(INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, DAMAGES FOR LOSS OF PROFITS, BUSINESS INTERRUPTION,
LOSS OF INFORMATION, INJURY OR DEATH) ARISING OUT OF THE USE OF OR INABILITY
TO USE THE MATERIALS, EVEN IF RPCD Holdings, LLC HAS BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY
OF SUCH LOSS OR DAMAGES.
DMCA Notice
RPCD Holdings, LLC respects the intellectual property of others.
If you believe that your copyrighted work has been copied in a way that constitutes
copyright infringement and is accessible on this site, you may notify our copyright
agent, as set forth in the Digital Millennium Copyright Act of 1998 (DMCA).
For your complaint to be valid under the DMCA, you must provide the following
information when providing notice of the claimed copyright infringement:
* A physical or electronic signature of a person authorized to act on behalf
of the copyright owner Identification of the copyrighted work claimed to have
been infringed
* Identification of the material that is claimed to be infringing or to be
the subject of the infringing activity and that is to be removed
* Information reasonably sufficient to permit the service provider to contact
the complaining party, such as an address, telephone number, and, if available,
an electronic mail address
* A statement that the complaining party "in good faith believes that
use of the material in the manner complained of is not authorized by the copyright
owner, its agent, or law"
* A statement that the "information in the notification is accurate",
and "under penalty of perjury, the complaining party is authorized to act
on behalf of the owner of an exclusive right that is allegedly infringed"
The above information must be submitted as a written, faxed or emailed notification to the following Designated Agent:
Attn: DMCA Office
RPCD Holdings, LLC
support@practicetechnologies.com
WE CAUTION YOU THAT UNDER FEDERAL LAW, IF YOU KNOWINGLY MISREPRESENT THAT
ONLINE MATERIAL IS INFRINGING, YOU MAY BE SUBJECT TO HEAVY CIVIL PENALTIES.
THESE INCLUDE MONETARY DAMAGES, COURT COSTS, AND ATTORNEYS’ FEES INCURRED
BY US, BY ANY COPYRIGHT OWNER, OR BY ANY COPYRIGHT OWNER’S LICENSEE THAT IS INJURED AS A RESULT OF OUR RELYING UPON YOUR MISREPRESENTATION. YOU MAY ALSO
BE SUBJECT TO CRIMINAL PROSECUTION FOR PERJURY.
This information should not be construed as legal advice, for further details
on the information required for valid DMCA notifications, see 17 U.S.C. 512(c)(3).
Questions/Comments | support@practicetechnologies.com
